{
    "subject": "resource/Ysgol_John_Bright",
    "predicate": "ontology/country",
    "object": "resource/United_Kingdom",
    "human_readable": "Ysgol John Bright is located in the United Kingdom.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9357337355613708,
            "question": "Where is Ysgol John Bright located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9282116889953613,
            "question": "In which country is Ysgol John Bright situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6141102313995361,
            "question": "What type of institution is Ysgol John Bright?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45308834314346313,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Ysgol John Bright?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39279699325561523,
            "question": "Is Ysgol John Bright a school?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31834322214126587,
            "question": "What is the educational level of Ysgol John Bright?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3136909008026123,
            "question": "Is Ysgol John Bright a well-known school?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28446370363235474,
            "question": "Are there any notable alumni from Ysgol John Bright?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2468690425157547,
            "question": "What language(s) are spoken at Ysgol John Bright?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13465584814548492,
            "question": "Does Ysgol John Bright offer extracurricular activities?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ysgol John Bright is located in the United Kingdom.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9273_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What language(s) are spoken at Ysgol John Bright?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9273_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable alumni from Ysgol John Bright?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9273_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Ysgol John Bright a well-known school?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9273_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9273_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9273_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9273_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9273_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9273_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9273_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9273_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9273_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9273_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9273_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format with the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that Ysgol John Bright is a High school in Llandudno, which is located in Wales, UK (LL30 1LF, United Kingdom). This suggests that Ysgol John Bright is indeed located in the United Kingdom."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Ysgol John Bright is located at Maesdu Rd, Llandudno LL30 1LF, United Kingdom. Therefore, the statement \"Ysgol John Bright is located in the United Kingdom\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}